<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Python on Zeeyad Rahman</title>
    <link>https://zeeyad.github.io/tags/python/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Python on Zeeyad Rahman</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 23 Feb 2025 10:39:20 +0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://zeeyad.github.io/tags/python/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Bringing Creatures to Life: My Illustration Process for GetWildlifeArt</title>
      <link>https://zeeyad.github.io/posts/2025_process-creation-for-getwildlifeart/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Feb 2025 10:39:20 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://zeeyad.github.io/posts/2025_process-creation-for-getwildlifeart/</guid>
      <description>Step 1: Generating AI Art with Leonardo AI 🛠️ I start by using prompt engineering in Leonardo AI to generate detailed and unique wildlife and fantasy illustrations. The goal is to get a strong foundation that I can refine later.
Alternative option to Leonardo AI:
 MidJourney Stable Diffusion  Step 2: Extracting &amp;amp; Organizing Images with Python 🤖 Once I have a batch of AI-generated images, I use Python scripts to extract individual illustrations, making it easier to process them efficiently.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wildlife Art</title>
      <link>https://zeeyad.github.io/projects/2025_wildlifeart/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Feb 2025 12:02:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://zeeyad.github.io/projects/2025_wildlifeart/</guid>
      <description>WildlifeArt offers high-quality vector and digital illustrations of animals and mythical creatures, designed for use in both digital and print projects. Our assets are perfect for web projects, branding, advertising campaigns, scrapbooking, card making, sublimation, and digital planners. They can also be used for merchandise, such as t-shirts, stickers, and posters.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Trading Analysis Dashboard</title>
      <link>https://zeeyad.github.io/projects/2024_trading_analysis_dashboard/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 12:02:26 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://zeeyad.github.io/projects/2024_trading_analysis_dashboard/</guid>
      <description>Trading Analysis Dashboard built on Fundamental, Technical and Sentimental Analysis to detect Entry and Exit signals.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Brunei Work</title>
      <link>https://zeeyad.github.io/projects/2023_bruneiwork/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Apr 2023 12:02:31 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://zeeyad.github.io/projects/2023_bruneiwork/</guid>
      <description>      Brunei Work is an AI-powered Search Engine to find the latest job vacancy in Brunei. The site officially launched on 10th April 2023 by posting on the Brunei Subreddit. Follow for weekly job post highlights on the instagram
Technology Stack
 Front-end: HTML, CSS, Javascript, Bootstrap Back-end: Ruby on Rails, Python Database: PostgreSQL  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Average Property Prices in Brunei</title>
      <link>https://zeeyad.github.io/posts/2022_average-property-prices-in-brunei/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Nov 2022 11:56:21 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://zeeyad.github.io/posts/2022_average-property-prices-in-brunei/</guid>
      <description>I’ve collected a small datasets of around 3,000 property listing from 23 different Property Agents such as G.A Real Estate Agency, Bruworld Real Estate and Property Management Sdn Bhd, Bess Perfect Property Agency, Valor Property, Homestage Realty, Pan Villa and various agencies.
From my findings, the top 3 most popular property listing type are:  2-Storey Detached House. 2-Storey Semi-Detached House. 2-Storey Terrace House.    I’ve selected the top 10 locations with the most property listing count for each of the popular property type so as to have an accurate representation of the average prices at each location.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Muslim Converts in Brunei</title>
      <link>https://zeeyad.github.io/posts/2022_muslim-converts-in-brunei/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Oct 2022 11:56:31 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://zeeyad.github.io/posts/2022_muslim-converts-in-brunei/</guid>
      <description>Sources Dataset from Brunei Department of Statistics
Link: https://deps.mofe.gov.bn/SitePages/edata%20Library.aspx
Software Credits To SJ Data Viz
Link: https://www.sjdataviz.com/software</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
